https://www.warm-glass.co.uk/security-privacy-cookies-cms-103.html

Please Log In
Email Address:
Password:
Forgot your password?
Hop on board...
ABOUT SSL CERTIFICATES
Are you a new Customer? Click here to register.
Register
Hello. Login
to see your Loyalty Discount.
Discounts
Currencies:
Norwegian Kr
Language:
Hello. Login
to see your Loyalty Discount.
Fahrenheit to Celsius Converter
Home  »
Security, Privacy & Cookies
Security & Privacy and Cookies
Our website is checked daily by an approved scanning vendor for security threats, and the latest security certificates are displayed on our Home page.  All personal information entered online will be treated securely, please read our Privacy Policy for details:
Privacy Policy
1 We will deal with personal information securely and respectfully. All online transaction information will be encrypted using 128-bit SSL certificates. No cardholder information will be passed unencrypted and we will not see card details when an Order is placed online. We will ensure that none of your personal information can be examined, used or modified by any third parties attempting to gain access to sensitive information.
2 To process an Order, we will need your name, billing address, telephone number, email address and credit card information. We will use this information to process the Order and, if any questions should arise, will contact you about your Order.
3 If we need to contact you, we will contact you via email first. If unsuccessful (or time is critical), we will try to contact you by telephone.
4 Any information provided by you will be used for the purposes of processing your Orders only. To achieve this we reserve the right to provide your details to third parties that are involved in processing the Order or for delivering specific services to you (for example, the financial institution that issued its credit card or the courier that delivers the Order).
5 Your information will not be shared with individuals or other companies (such as direct mail organisations or other third parties) unless required by law.
6 We use analytical data from our website to monitor how people interact with our website in order to improve our service. This data is strictly for internal use only. We also use your account data to provide our loyalty bonus scheme.
7 If you have requested to receive our newsletter, this will be delivered to the email address you give us. We send newsletters approximately once per week with information on products, courses, discounts and news about the glass community. We may also occasionally send specific offers we believe may be of interest to you based on your interaction with our website (for example a discount offer on a product you have viewed on our website). These will be for our products. We will not share your details with other individuals or companies unless required by law.
8 You should help us update and maintain the accuracy of any of our personal information by using the account profile pages or notifying us of any changes of address, title, telephone number or e-mail address. If you are no longer a customer and you wish to be removed from our database please request this via our 'Contact Us' page. This will mean that you will lose any loyalty discount or privileges on future purchases and any spend until that point will not count towards any future loyalty bonus should you become a customer again in the future.
9 If you no longer wish to be on our mailing list then you can unsubscribe very easily using the 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of our newsletter emails and we will remove you from the list.
Cookies
Cookies are small bits of text used by a browser to store information on our computer hard drive.
Each cookie can only be read by the web server that originally issued it.
Cookies cannot profile your system or collect information from your hard drive. Most on-line retailers use cookies.
We use cookies to show whether you are a prior customer and therefore will not need to re-enter certain information every time you shop on our website. We also use cookies to monitor how our website is used by visitors in order to help us improve our service. We will not use cookies to store credit card numbers or other payment information.
Registered office: 5 Havyat Park, Wrington, Bristol, BS40 5PA, UK
Company Reg No. 5365166. VAT No. 791350132
Customer Service
Customer Service Home
Contact Us
Delivery
Returns
Breakage Cover
Discounts and Loyalty Scheme
Working at Warm Glass
What our customers say...
Join us on facebook
Join us on instagram
Join us on Youtube
Call Us
Stay up to date See weekly offers, new products and more…Enter your email address to subscribe to our Newsletter! Currencies
Euro
GB Pound
Swedish Kr
Danish Kr
Norwegian Kr
Testimonials
Second or third order with you. So glad my work colleague recommended you. Angie S.09 December 2020
Fantastic service as always. Thank you Warm Glass! Agnieszka K.09 December 2020
I have just bought some powders, pea pod green, so that I can extend my landscape pictures. The powders are really versatile and the colours are great! Alison T.09 December 2020
Great site, easy to navigate. Jean C.08 December 2020
Fantastic service, well packaged and quick delivery. Lesley D.08 December 2020
Clearly set out and easy to use. I can find everything easily. The knowledge base is excellent and I found the video about choosing a plug in kiln very useful and well presented. Great company! Melanie B.08 December 2020
© Warm Glass UK, 2015-2018Registered office: 5 Havyat Park, Wrington, Bristol, BS40 5PA, UK
Company Reg No. 5365166. VAT No. 791350132
×Close
Loading results...
